Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Vietnam War, 1944-2001
  - Subseries VII:A: Vietnam War Material, 1944-2001
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1968 Hanoi - Prisoner Release - Correspondence, 1967-1970; cuid16280 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1968 Hanoi - Prisoner Release - Photographs, cuid16281 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1972, 1972-1973; cuid16282 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: Notebooks, [1968]; cuid16283 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: Notebooks, [1972]; cuid16284 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Subseries VII:B: The Pentagon Papers, 1971-1976
    - Clippings, 1971-1972, 1976, undated; cuid16285 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Clippings: Supreme Court Upholds Publication, 1971; cuid16286 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Clippings: Trial of Anthony J. Russo, Jr. and Daniel Ellsberg, 1973; cuid16287 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Clippings, Zinn Notes and Related Materials (includes copy of Zinn subpoena), 1971-1975, undated; cuid16288 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Court Documents: USA v. The New York Times, et al. - Amicus Curiae Brief, 1971; cuid16289 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg, 1971-1973; cuid16290 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit I Volume I "Vietnam and the US 1940-1950" (I), [1973]; cuid16291 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit I Volume I "Vietnam and the US 1940-1950" (II), [1973]; cuid16292 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit II Volume II "US Involvement in the Franco-Viet Minh War", [1973]; cuid16293 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit III Volume IV A.2 "Aid for France in Indochina", [1973]; cuid16294 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit IV Volume IV A.3 "US and France's Withdrawal from Vietnam 1954-1956", [1973]; cuid16295 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit 9 Volume IV B.5 "The Overthrow of Ngo Dinh Diem, May-Nov, 1963" (I), [1973]; cuid16296 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit 9 Volume IV B.5 "The Overthrow of Ngo Dinh Diem, May-Nov, 1963" (II), [1973]; cuid16297 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Zinn Testimony (includes notes and clippings), 1973; cuid16298 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - "Daniel Ellsberg and the Power of the Peacemakers" by Stewart Burns (draft and letter to Zinn), 1977; cuid16299 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - House Committee on Government Operations: FOIA Reports, 1972, 1973; cuid16300 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Availability of Information to Congress, Apr 1973; cuid16301 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Part 4 and Part 5, Mar 6, 1972-Mar 28, 1972; cuid16302 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Part 6 and Part 7, Apr 11, 1972-May 11, 1972; cuid16303 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - The Pentagon Papers (Part 1 and Part 2), Jun 23, 1971-Jun 29, 1971; cuid16304 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - The Pentagon Papers (Part 3), Jun 30 and Jul 7, 1971; cuid16305 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Problems of Congress in Obtaining Information from the Executive Branch (Part 8), May 12, 1972-Jun 1, 1972; cuid16306 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Notes, undated; cuid16307 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - A Pentagon Papers Digest, Indochina Information Project, undated; cuid16308 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Publication Announcement, 1971; cuid16309 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume I (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16310 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume II (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16311 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume III (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16312 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume IV (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16313 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume V (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), 1972; cuid16314 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume V - Review, 1974; cuid16315 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - The Pentagon Papers, The New York Times Series (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), 1971; cuid16316 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Russo, Anthony, 1973, 1995, undated; cuid16317 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - "Servants of the State": Studs Terkel Interview with Daniel Ellsberg, Anthony Russo and Eqbal Ahmad, 1972; cuid16318 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Series VIII: Subject Files, 1933-2010
  This series contains materials on a wide range of topics, representing either research for books, articles and lectures or merely items clipped and saved based on Zinn's many personal interests. Some of the largest subject areas are the Gulf Wars, Central America, the Central Intelligence Agency, civil liberties, crime and punishment, East Asia (especially China), prisons, terrorism and trials (including many at which Zinn provided testimony). There are many folders which Zinn labeled either "Hope" or "Resistance"; they contain collected articles, clippings, flyers, notes and individual documents describing various events or acts of resistance which appeared to him to be reasons for hope and optimism.
  Some of the materials in this series, particularly newspaper clippings, are in poor condition. Also, because Zinn's method of clipping articles sometimes meant merely saving the portion of interest to him, many pieces are incomplete and may lack publication title and/or date.
  - Abortion (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16319 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Academic Contacts, 1973-1975, undated; cuid16320 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Academic Freedom: Accuracy in Academia, 1985-1987, undated; cuid16321 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Academic Freedom: Accuracy in Academia - Reader, Mark, 1985; cuid16322 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Academic Freedom: Accuracy in Academia - Zinn Appearance on Today Show (correspondence), 1985; cuid16323 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Action, 1971-1974, undated; cuid16324 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Action Strategies, 1963-1969; cuid16325 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Action Strategies, 1970-1979, undated; cuid16326 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Africa, 1960-1965; cuid16327 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Africa, 1967, undated; cuid16328 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Africa: Zimbabwe: A New History, 1982; cuid16329 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Agnew, Spiro T.: Conviction and Sentence, 1973; cuid16330 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, Massachusetts (CLUM): Zinn Notes in Preparation for Speech, undated; cuid16331 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - American Historical Association (AHA) and the Radical Historians Caucus, 1969-Mar 1970; cuid16332 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - American Historical Association (AHA) and the Radical Historians Caucus, Apr 1970-1976, undated; cuid16333 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Anarchism, 1968-1982, undated; cuid16334 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Anarchism: American Anarchism, 1971-1981, undated; cuid16335 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Anarchism: Bibliography, 1969-1975; cuid16336 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Anarchism: "Introduction I", 1968-1977, undated; cuid16337 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Anarchism: Spanish Anarchists (Spanish Civil War), 1986-1988; cuid16338 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Anti-Communism, 1950-1959; cuid16339 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Anti-Communism, 1983-2002, undated; cuid16340 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Communism: House Un-American Activities Committee (HUAC), 1963, undated; cuid16341 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Anti-Communism: Informers, 1955-1956, 1961; cuid16342 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Art and Politics, 1968-1989; cuid16343 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Art and Politics, 1990-2005; cuid16344 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Art and Politics, undated; cuid16345 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Art and Politics: Artists, 2001-2007, undated; cuid16346 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Art and Politics: Artists and War, 1995-2008, undated; cuid16347 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Art and Politics: Literature, 1953, 1963-1981; cuid16348 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Art and Politics: Literature (notes, summaries, excerpts of books, films, poetry), undated; cuid16349 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Art and Politics: Protest Literature, 1988-2005, undated; cuid16350 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Art and Politics: War and Art, 2002-2007, undated; cuid16351 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Bakunin, Michael, 1976, 1985, undated; cuid16352 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Barrett, James W., 1972-1975, undated; cuid16353 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Barrett, James W.: Court Documents, 1974, 1995-1996; cuid16354 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Berrigan, Daniel and Philip Berrigan, 1970-1978, 2002, 2003, undated; cuid16355 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Berrigan, Daniel and Philip Berrigan: Danbury Photograph of Daniel, undated; cuid16356 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Buckley, Jr., William F.: Articles and Notes, 1970-1971, undated; cuid16357 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Buber, Martin: Excerpt from The Letters of Martin Buber: A Life of Dialogue, 1996; cuid16358 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Bush, George W. Administration, 1999-2005, undated; cuid16359 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bush, George W. Administration, 2000-2005; cuid16360 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Bush, George W. Administration, 2007, undated; cuid16361 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Bush, George W. Administration: Foreign Policy, May 2001-Dec 2001; cuid16362 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Bush, George W. Administration: Impeachment, 2006, undated; cuid16363 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Calendars (commemorative): Julius C.C. Edelstein and Women's Leadership (in Spanish), 2003, 2006; cuid16364 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1976-1979, undated; cuid16365 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Carter, Jimmy: "'76 Politics", 1975-1978, undated; cuid16366 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights (CCR): Fall 1999 Docket, cuid16367 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair), 1987-2001, undated; cuid16368 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): "Contragate and Foreign Policy Overview", 1984-1994, undated; cuid16369 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): "Deception Law and Contragate", 1984-1991, undated; cuid16370 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): Hasenfus, Eugene, 1985-1987; cuid16371 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): Iran-Reagan Crisis, 1986-1987, undated; cuid16372 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Central America: History, 1990-1992, undated; cuid16373 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Central America: History (clippings), 1984-2009, undated; cuid16374 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Central America: Law, 1981-1985, undated; cuid16375 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Central America: In Contempt of Congress, The Reagan Record of Deceit and Illegality on Central America, 1985; cuid16376 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Central America: Nicaragua, 1983-1988, undated; cuid16377 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Central America: Panama (includes letter from John Kerry), 1989-1991, 2003, undated; cuid16378 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1973-1985, undated; cuid16379 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: "Bizarre Activities and Lies", 1976, 1978, 1983, undated; cuid16380 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: The CIA and the Cult of Intelligence by Marchetti and Marks (with several news clippings), 1974, [1977], 1978; cuid16381 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Hearings Volumes 1 and 2, Sep 1975; cuid16382 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Hearings Volumes 2 and 4, Sep 1975-Oct 1975; cuid16383 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Hearings Volume 6, Nov 1975; cuid16384 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Interim Report "Alleged Assassination Plots Involving Foreign Leaders", Nov 1975; cuid16385 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book I "Foreign and Military Intelligence, Apr 1976; cuid16386 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book III "Supplementary Detailed Staff Reports on Intelligence Activities and the Rights of Americans", Apr 1976; cuid16387 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book IV "Supplementary Detailed Staff Reports on Foreign and Military Intelligence", Apr 1976; cuid16388 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book VI "Supplementary Reports on Intelligence Activities", Apr 1976; cuid16389 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Iran Contra - Breeden, BIll, 1986-1990, 1992, undated; cuid16390 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Iran Contra - Bush, George, 1986, 1989, undated; cuid16391 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Massachusetts (CLUM) Free Speech Controversy, 1987, undated; cuid16392 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Overview, 1973-1977, undated; cuid16393 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: The Press, 1977, 1986, undated; cuid16394 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Surveillance, 1965-1978, 2000, undated; cuid16395 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Various News Clippings, 1967-1976; cuid16396 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Various News Clippings, 1976-1993, undated; cuid16397 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Children in Need of Services (CHINS) Reform in Massachusetts, undated; cuid16398 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Chile: 1973 Coup, 1972-1976, undated; cuid16399 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Chile: 1973 Coup - Aftermath, 1973-1987, 1998-2001, undated; cuid16400 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Chomsky, Noam, 1967-1998, undated; cuid16401 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Civil Disobedience, 1949, 1961-1983; cuid16402 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Civil Disobedience, 1985-1999; cuid16403 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Civil Disobedience, undated; cuid16404 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Civil Disobedience: Burlington, Civil Disobedience and the Law, 1968, 1984-1988, undated; cuid16405 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Civil Disobedience: McCrackin, Maurice, 1975-1984; cuid16406 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Civil Disobedience: Notes, undated; cuid16407 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Civil Disobedience: Otis Air National Guard Base Demonstrations / Trials (protest US intervention in Central America and dumping of toxic chemicals), 1986-1987; cuid16408 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - AVCO Plowshares 7, 1983-1985; cuid16409 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Griffiss Plowshares 7, 1984-1985; cuid16410 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Plowshares 4, 1982-1983; cuid16411 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Plowshares 8, 1981-1990; cuid16412 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Plowshares 8 Resentencing Transcript, 1990; cuid16413 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Trident II Pruning Hooks, 1984-1986; cuid16414 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Various Actions, 1984-1985, 1997-1999; cuid16415 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Civil Disobedience: Walzer (Michael) Essay, 1968-1969, undated; cuid16416 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Civil Liberties, 1989-1991; cuid16417 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties, 1995-1999; cuid16418 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties, 2000-2001; cuid16419 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties, 2002; cuid16420 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Civil Liberties, 2003; cuid16421 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Civil Liberties, 2004; cuid16422 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Civil Liberties, 2005; cuid16423 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Civil Liberties, 2006; cuid16424 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Civil Liberties, Jan 2007-May 2007; cuid16425 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Civil Liberties, Jun 2007-Dec 2007; cuid16426 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Civil Liberties, 2008, undated; cuid16427 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Civil Liberties: Academic Freedom, 1949-1967; cuid16428 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Civil Liberties: Academic Freedom, 1970-1987, undated; cuid16429 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Civil Liberties: Academic Freedom - Kraus, Arthur J. Case, 1958, 1967-1972; cuid16430 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Civil Liberties: Bari, Judy and Darryl Cherney Case, 2001-2002; cuid16431 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Civil Liberties: Fifth Amendment, 1953-1956; cuid16432 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Civil Liberties: First Amendment - Falk, Richard Case and Earl Caldwell Case, 1970, 1971; cuid16433 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech from 1798-1917 (notes and fragments), undated; cuid16434 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech - Law, 1975-2002, undated; cuid16435 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech Lecture, 1975-1987, undated; cuid16436 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech - National Security, 1969-1989, undated; cuid16437 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Civil Liberties: Guantanamo, Torture, Media, 2008; cuid16438 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Civil Liberties: "Homefront Confidential" White Paper by the Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, 2002; cuid16439 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1959-1969; cuid16440 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1971-1974; cuid16441 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1975; cuid16442 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1976; cuid16443 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1977; cuid16444 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1978-1980, undated; cuid16445 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties: Speech - Extralegal, 1963-1976, 1989, undated; cuid16446 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Civil War (articles), 2008-2009; cuid16447 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: Various, 1961-1989; cuid16448 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Various, 1990-2001; cuid16449 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Clippings: Various, 2001-2009, undated; cuid16450 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Columbus, Christopher: "Celebrate Columbus" - James Victore Poster, 1992, 2007; cuid16451 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Columbus, Christopher: "The Christopher Columbus Follies, an Eco-Cabaret", 1992; cuid16452 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Columbus, Indians and Expansion, 1991-1993, undated; cuid16453 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Columbus, the Indians and Human Progress (German translation of section from A People's History of the United States), [1992]; cuid16454 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Columbus, Christopher: "Constructing and Deconstructing the Historical Myths of Columbus..." by Donald A. Grinde, Jr., [1993]; cuid16455 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Correspondence, 1990-1992; cuid16456 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Notes, Articles, 1989-1992, undated; cuid16457 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Notes, Drafts and Fragments, undated; cuid16458 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Quincentennial, 1990-1992, undated; cuid16459 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Quincentennial Protests, 1991-1992; cuid16460 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Quincentennial Protests - Early Protest at Florida Museum of Natural History, 1989-1990; cuid16461 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Resources, 1989-1998, undated; cuid16462 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Rethinking Columbus, 1991; cuid16463 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Zinn Writings, 1991-1992, undated; cuid16464 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Communism (clippings), 1990; cuid16465 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Crime and Punishment, 1969-1986; cuid16466 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Crime and Punishment, 1991-2000; cuid16467 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Crime and Punishment, 2001-2008; cuid16468 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Crime and Punishment, undated; cuid16469 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Crime and Punishment: Abu-Jamal, Mumia, 1995-2000, undated; cuid16470 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment, 1973-1999; cuid16471 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment (includes letter from Russ Feingold), 2000-2009, undated; cuid16472 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment - ...Last Meal by Jacquelyn C. Black, 2003; cuid16473 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment - Zinn Writing and Notes, undated; cuid16474 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Crime and Punishment: "Class and the Economics of Crime" by David M. Gordon (two versions), 1971; cuid16475 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Crime and Punishment: Crime and Social Justice, A Journal of Radical Criminology, Spring-Summer 1974; cuid16476 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Crime and Punishment: Municipal Court - General, 1971-1973, undated; cuid16477 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Crime and Punishment: Municipal Court - "Melodrama in Dorchester in Five Acts," Student Paper by Julie Ann Hankin, 1972-1973; cuid16478 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Cuba, 1978, 1994, 2000-2004, undated; cuid16479 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Cuba: Missile Crisis, 1960-1963, 1998, undated; cuid16480 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Cuba: Vocabulary, 2004, undated; cuid16481 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Dioxin Poisoning (Agent Orange), 1978-1984, undated; cuid16482 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - "Domestic Ironies", 1999-2004, undated; cuid16483 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Draft Resistance, 1966-1972, undated; cuid16484 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Draft Resistance, 1980-1984, undated; cuid16485 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Drinnon, Richard, 1986; cuid16486 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - East Asia: Cambodia, 1958-1959; cuid16487 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - East Asia: China - Border Regions (includes Owen Lattimore materials), 1957-1966, undated; cuid16488 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - East Asia: China - Chiang Kai-shek, 1947-1962, undated; cuid16489 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - East Asia: China - Chinese Language, 1943-1961, undated; cuid16490 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - East Asia: China - Chinese Thought (religion and philosophy), 1958-1960, undated; cuid16491 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - East Asia: China - Civil Liberties, 1957-1960, undated; cuid16492 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - East Asia: China - Confucian Economy, undated; cuid16493 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - East Asia: China - Confucian Thought, undated; cuid16494 (Box 47, Folder 1)